nri.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy | Nomura Research Institute (NRI)

This policy contains the basic guidelines concerning personal data collected and used by Nomura Research Institute, Ltd., and its group companies (hereinafter collectively referred to as the "NRI Group").

As a company handling personal data, the NRI Group has established the following "Personal Data Protection Statement" for processing personal data (meaning data concerning living individuals including data that enables the identification of the relevant person by name, date of birth, other statements, a number assigned to each person, etc., that are included in said data). The NRI Group shall observe the Law Concerning the Protection of Personal Information, other applicable laws and ordinances and this privacy policy. 

Personal Data Protection Statement   
Usage Purposes  
Upon specifying the purposes for use to the maximum extent possible, the NRI Group shall use personal data within the framework of the following purposes, except in cases in which the prior consent of the relevant person was obtained and in which the handling of said personal data is permitted as exceptional cases by the Law Concerning the Protection of Personal Information and/or other applicable laws and ordinances.  |  |  | Providing NRI Group’s products and services, such as research activities, consulting services (concerning management, business operations, information systems, etc.), development and operation of information systems and computer network systems, information processing services, content services and information provision services.  
---|---|---  
|  | Delivery of our publications such as Chiteki shisan sozo (Knowledge Creation and Integration), IT soryushon frontia (IT Solutions Frontier), etc.  
|  | Providing information about new products and services  
|  | Providing notifications of our company’s latest information, various seminars and exhibitions  
|  | Sending questionnaires on customer satisfaction, etc.  
|  | Implementing marketing and promotional campaigns  
|  | Management of contracts with customers  
|  | Management of information on stockholders  
|  | Employment (including recruiting) and personnel affairs management  
|  | Handling and processing the entrusted data including personal information  
  
If the need arises to use personal data for purposes other than those specified above, consent of the relevant person shall be obtained for said purpose, except in cases in which the prior consent of the person was obtained or in which the handling of said personal data is permitted as an exceptional case by the Law Concerning the Protection of Personal Information and/or other applicable laws and ordinances.

The NRI Group may use a contractor to implement part of a service and may disclose personal data within the necessary range to such contractor. In this case, the NRI Group shall implement appropriate management in accordance with law and the standards determined by the NRI Group.

The NRI Group may record conversations with customers. 

Disclosure to Third Parties  
The NRI Group shall not provide or disclose personal data collected by the NRI Group to any third party, except in cases where any of the following applies:

Disclosure, Correction and Discontinuation of Use of Entered Contents  
At the request of the relevant person, the NRI Group shall disclose personal data to the person as long as proper implementation of our business activities is not hindered. In this case, we shall confirm the identity of the person by the method prescribed by the NRI Group.

If erroneous content is included in the disclosed personal data, the NRI Group shall immediately correct such content. In addition, if the relevant person requests discontinuation of the use of the personal data of said person, we shall immediately discontinue such use.

Website Security  
SSL data encryption technology is used as a security measure to prevent interception on the network when personal data is provided on the website.

| SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) is a common protocol used as a security measure for communication on the website. It prevents the interception of data by encrypting it before it is sent over the Internet.   
---|---  
  
Although the NRI Group shall make utmost efforts in the management of personal data, we are unable to fully guarantee the secrecy of personal data because of the nature of the Internet and e-mail. Due consideration should be given to this point in the use of websites and e-mail.

Privacy Policy for Each Product and Service  
In some cases, a privacy policy (such as the purposes of the use of personal data, third-party disclosure, security and contact information) is stipulated for each product, service, etc., at websites for such products and services, and in e-mail messages and various notifications. If provisions that are different from those of this privacy policy and/or special provisions are included, the privacy policy stipulated for each product or service shall take precedence over this privacy policy.

Updates  
This privacy policy is subject to change without prior notice due to the amendment of applicable laws and/or ordinances, changes in the policies of the NRI Group, etc
